Let's see. Bradley tank.
Transport truck. Batmobile.
(Sheldon:)- Ooh!
- No.
(Howard:)Here we go. Red 2006 Ford Taurus
on the streets of Pasadena.
(Leonard:)Uh...
(Raj:)- What?
- Statistically, red cars...
(Sheldon:)...are stopped by police
far more often than any other color.
(Sheldon:)I don't want any hassles with the fuzz.
Fine, what color do you want?
(Sheldon:)You know the pale blue
of Luke Skywalker's lightsaber?
(Sheldon:)Before it was digitally remastered.
(Howard:)Black it is.
Okay. Now, what you wanna do first
is turn on the ignition and shift into drive.
(Sheldon:)I haven't fastened my seat belt yet.
(Leonard:)Okay, fasten your seat belt.
(Sheldon:)Click.
(Sheldon:)- Are there air bags?
- You don't need air bags.